Aashir khan

A Position in dynamic and well reputed organization which offers good opportunities and challenging working environment, which in return would help me in building up my career, knowledge and experience in my profession. I am a passionate person who knows how to complete the tasks with emotional involvement till the very End-Situations in different environments.

aashirkhan961@gmail.com 🔀

03200461281

Madni street no.11 House no.24/47/3k/c Ali Muhammad
Park Tajpura, Madni street no.11 House no.24/47/3k/c Ali
Muhammad Park Tajpura, LAHORE, Pakistan

10 March, 1998 ##

linkedin.com/in/aashirkhan in

facebook.com/aashirkhan

github.com/ashirkhan961 🌎

instagram.com/aashirkhan 🧿

EDUCATION

Matric

Govt. Boys High School Tajpura

2011 - 2013

Lahore, Pakistan Marks(582/1050)

DAE (Electrical)

Pak Poly Technical Institute of Technology

2013 - 2016 Lahore, Pakistan Marks(2766/3550)

BSCS

Lahore Garrison University

2016 - 2020 Lahore, Pakistan CGPA (2.87)

Final Year Project

 Final Year Project: I have completed my final year project by making the (LGU Official and Social Application) of the university by using Flutter and dart language on Visual studio and Android Studio plateform.

WORK EXPERIENCE

(6 Months)

Offside Technologies

01/2021 - Present Lahore, Pakistan

Employee as a Junior Shopify front-end Developer.

Tasks

- Employee as a Junior Shopify front-end Developer.
- Bug's Fixes

Internee (3 Months)

Arfa karim Tower

07/2019 - 09/2019

Lahore

Ideas/Tasks

- I work with the startup, who is working under government projects (PITB) in Plan9 with the support of PITB. The startup name was "lamChef", where the idea is to encourage the housewife's or male chef's to making the homemade food and delivery to anywhere or donate to the needy persons as well.
- Therefore, our CEO needs a responsive website or a Application for this, so with the help of our CEO i build UI/UX designs of the application which is my part in the whole project.

TOOLS/SKILLS

Sublime VS Code
HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP UI/UX
Wordpress Shopify

WORDPRESS PROJECTS

Catalyicsecurity

Coatscountry

Easypockets

Offside Technology

ORGANIZATIONS

Sumato Sulotions

Zasa Solutions

Arfa Karim Tower

Offside Technologies

CERTIFICATES

PITB's Technology Incubator's startup "iamChef" as an Internee. (07/2019 - 09/2019)

I was designing a laypout of randoom website by using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, & JavaScript . During this time period i worked on the Designing.

LANGUAGES

HTML			0	0
CSS			0	0
Bootstrap	0	0	0	0
Shopify Liquid		0	0	0

INTERESTS

Own Business Army (Capton)

Traveling